Kettle and Idols
I've always loved this one, but I've loved it since I started idolizing,
I think it is possible to stop at that moment, isn't it? Food samples.
That's why I like cream soda,
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about the guest.
I'm sorry. What are you talking about?
I'll stop in a moment.
Yes, when you stop, the bouldering of doom comes.
Let me put it this way, Mr. Kettle,
I see.
The moment the water is flowing out, there is a food sample as a work of art,
Or there is an icing here,
It's a moment that can only be created with food samples,
I was very moved by the idea of creating a moment that only food samples can do,
And it's cute, isn't it? It's so realistic.
Do you understand?
Real is cute?
It's a challenge, isn't it?
No, no, no.
I'm sorry about the cute part.
May I ask you something?
I haven't even reached that point.
I wonder what it is.
Maybe a food sample is to show the cutest part of food.
It is a three-dimensional object that captures a moment.
Recently, accessories are also becoming popular,
So, there is a trend to use food samples as accessories.
For example, rings,
And also, there is this Neapolitan food sample here,
And you can even get a catsuit with a Neapolitan on it,
Neapolitan?
But if it was a gekisha game, it would work.
Maybe you could go back with a fork or something.
That would be really cute,
When I thought about what I have to offer,
I thought, "Idols and food samples are the only things I can do,
Idols and food samples?
It's true that the meaning of the word "food sample" is a three-dimensional object that represents the most delicious part of the food for the customers' security, right?
I see. So it's about capturing the moment.
Am I right?
Do you understand?
Yes, it is.
But I just don't get the "cute" part.
Really?
I see what you mean.
You're using the word "cute" to convey that?
Yeah. It's cute.
I see.
So, I'm thinking of becoming a food sample craftsman when I really have no more questions.
I want her to learn the technique, though,
What about capturing a moment of yourself?
Your real self?
Real myself. So, food samples are also figures. If that's the case, then...
Yes, that's right.
But I also like realistic figures.
I like realistic figures too.
So I think I probably like realistic figures.
I like to think that the human hand can create something this realistic.
Is that what you mean?
I guess. Maybe.
So you are saying that human hands are creating something that is close to the peak of the moment.
That's right. That's right.
That's for sure. It's amazing when you say it like that.
Are you beginning to understand?
It's true.
I'm getting it. Is it just a big picture?
I need to understand more about the essence of what I'm talking about.
But I am happy. It's really wonderful, and I want to share it with everyone.
Ah~
I also listen to various things with my own sensitivity.
Really?
You draw pictures and so on.
I think it's interesting that you express yourself in this way.
I am glad to hear that. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. Does it sound superficial?
Not at all.
It sounds like we're both talking over each other.It's like we're talking over each other.
That's not true. Mr. Tachibana, please be serious and speak from the heart.
You are serious, aren't you?
I see, so the third one is food samples.
Yes, I see.
Tohoku-san will continue to work hard on this in Tohoku.
This program is...
Carrie
Ayaka
Mr. Hashi
Ms. Doko
and Kazukiku-san!
Thank you for all the love!
Come on, be more enthusiastic!